betaout.com 2019-03-29

# Privacy Policy - Betaout

Betaout is committed to protect your privacy, and rigorous procedures have been implemented to ensure this. The following Privacy Policy provides information on how your personal information is collected and used. 

### What this site does with the information it gathers/tracks: 

Betaout may offer several opportunities for visitors to register for promotional or informational mailings or to receive assistance in evaluating our software and services. Our site's optional information requests forms that require your name, company, e-mail address, as well as information to help us determine your needs relative to our products and services. 

Information submitted by you within our website, will be used only by us in order to provide customer support to you, inform you of any new promotion or update of our website, or to help process your order, in case help is needed. Betaout does not share, sell, rent, or trade PII with third parties for their promotional purposes. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

If you purchase a product or service from us, our credit card processing vendor will request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and physical address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date) in the following URL: http://www.paypal.com/. They utilize SSL encryption to transmit sensitive information. The information provided to them, will be only kept by them. Betaout will not have access to it. 

We use this information to send updates about our company and will contact you if requested or necessary. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. We also track browser types to help us understand our visitors' needs related to our website design. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. When you enter a contest or other promotional features, such as the Betaout's free trial, we ask for information such as your name, mailing address, daytime phone number and email address, so we can administer the contest and contact you to receive feedback regarding our product. 

We may also use your registered phone number occasionally to market and advertise our products and services that may be of interest to you including promotions, advertisements, competitions or commercial communications by text message via SMS. For details of how to opt out of marketing communications, please drop an email to [contact@betaout.com.](mailto:contact@betaout.com)" 

### Choice/Opt-out: 

If you sign up as a trial or a paying member, we request certain personally identifiable information from you. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and physical address). We use this information for promotion, or support purposes. The users selected to be part of Betaout's Case Studies have the option of opting-out by sending an email to [unsubscribe@Betaout.com](mailto:unsubscribe@betaout.com). However, all testimonials had full permission to be posted on www.Betaout.com. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter whether it is a promotional, support, or billing related communication, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at [unsubscribe@Betaout.com.](mailto:unsubscribe@betaout.com)

We offer an opportunity to opt-out of promotional, support, billing related communication emails, by clicking on the unsubscribe link on the emails. 

Every email sent through Betaout contains an easy, automated unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email. To unsubscribe, you simply need to click the link at the bottom of the page in the unsubscribe area. You are immediately excluded from all future mailings. 

### With whom this site shares information it gathers/tracks/shares: 

We share aggregate statistics about our customer's traffic patterns and reservations with our suppliers and partners, but these statistics do not include any personally identifying information. Like most Web sites, there is certain information we automatically track, including the URL that you just came from, which URL you go to next, the browser you are using and your IP address. 

Information gathered by our credit card processing vendor, as the name of the client, name of the company, phone number, email address, and credit card, is necessary for them to provide that service, and will not be provided to Betaout. Our credit card processing vendor is prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. 

We use cookies to help users navigate efficiently between secure and non-secure pages of our site. Cookies are pieces of information that a Website transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major web sites use them to provide useful features for their customers. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they identify a user's computer. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of a website if you do so. We link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

### Updating personally identifiable information: 

We intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. You have the option to register with Betaout for the use of our services. You can update your personal information, subscriptions or service package at any time by signing into your account and making the relevant adjustments. 

### Links to Other Sites: 

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Betaout. Please be aware that Betaout. is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. 

### Security: 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once they receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send us an email us to security@Betaout.com. 

###  How to Contact Us: 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, or would like more information about our company, please contact us at: [privacy@Betaout.com.](mailto:privacy@betaout.com)

This policy may be revised over time as new features are added to the web site. We will post those changes prominently so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. Please check this site for information about revisions to our privacy policy. If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner.
